Guide to the William Martin Religious Right research collection, 1975-2000 MS 537
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series II: Subject files, 1978-1996 (Boxes 77-91)
  - Subseries B: Other subject files
    - Sexual Education (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Scopes Trial (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Dwight Moody (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - SIECUS Report, 1995-1996 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Research Articles (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Political Research Associate Report: Constructing Homophobia (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Show #5 Stills (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Headlines/Research Articles (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Episode 6 - Research (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Archival Episodes 1, and 2 - Civil Rights (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Archival Episodes 1, and 2 - Billy Graham (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Archival Episodes 1, and 2 - JFK/Jackie (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Archival Episodes 1, and 2 - Nixon (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Archival Episodes 1, and 2 - Sex Ed/Anahiem (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Archival Episodes 1, and 2 - School Prayer (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Archival Episodes 1, and 2 - Space (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Archival Episodes 1, and 2 - Textbook/Kanawha (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Archival Episodes 3, and 4 - Carter Misc. (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Archival Episodes 3, and 4 - Born Again (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Archival Episodes 3, and 4 - ERA (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Archival Episodes 3, and 4 - White House Conference (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Archival Episodes 3, and 4 - Reagan (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Archival Episodes 3, and 4 - Election, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Archival Episodes 3, and 4 - School Prayer (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Archival Episodes 3, and 4 - Abortion (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Archival Episodes 3, and 4 - Evangelists (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Archival Episodes 3, and 4 - James Robinson (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Franklin Graham and Samaritan's Purse (1 of 2) Photos (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - Franklin Graham and Samaritan's Purse (2 of 2) (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Religious Television in America: Is Influence and Future (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - Harrell Tape Abstracts (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Miscellaneous Documents (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Bush - Gen (Box 91, Folder 24)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Robertson Campaign (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Bush/Clinton Inauguration (Box 91, Folder 26)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Gays in Military (Box 91, Folder 27)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Gunn Murder (Box 91, Folder 28)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Thomas (Box 91, Folder 29)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Hate Crimes (Box 91, Folder 30)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Promise Keepers (Box 91, Folder 31)
    - Archival Episode 6 - 2nd Amendment (Box 91, Folder 32)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Abortion Numbers (Box 91, Folder 33)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Dobson (Box 91, Folder 34)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Ralph Reed and Christian Coalition (Box 91, Folder 35)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Lake County (Box 91, Folder 36)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Operation Rescue (Box 91, Folder 37)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Republican National Convention, 1992 (Box 91, Folder 38)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Summitt (Box 91, Folder 39)
    - Archival Episode 6 - Late Randell Terry (Box 91, Folder 40)
    - Archival Episode 6: Religious Right in their Own Words (Box 91, Folder 41)
    - Archival Episode 6: Lee Atwater (Box 91, Folder 42)
    - Archival Episode 6: Abortion Numbers (Box 91, Folder 43)
    - Archival Episode 6: Amendment II (Box 91, Folder 44)
    - Archival Episode 6: Gary Bauer (Box 91, Folder 45)
    - Archival Episode 6: Bush (Box 91, Folder 46)
    - Archival Episode 6: Bush Defeat (Box 91, Folder 47)
    - Archival Episode 6: Paul Coverdale (Box 91, Folder 48)
    - Archival Episode 6: Republican National Convention, 1992 (Box 91, Folder 49)
    - Archival Episode 6: Christian Coalition (Box 91, Folder 50)
    - Archival Episode 6: Civil RR Victim (Box 91, Folder 51)
    - Archival Episode 6: Clinton (Box 91, Folder 52)
    - Archival Episode 6: Dr. Dobson (Box 91, Folder 53)
    - Archival Episode 6: Mike Farris/Home Schooling (Box 91, Folder 54)
    - Archival Episode 6: Gays in Military (Box 91, Folder 55)
    - Archival Episode 6: Gingrich (Box 91, Folder 56)
    - Archival Episode 6: David Gunn Murder (Box 91, Folder 57)
    - Archival Episode 6: Hate Crimes Bill (Box 91, Folder 58)
    - Archival Episode 6: Lake County/HART: Ramsey (Box 91, Folder 59)
    - Archival Episode 6: Promise Keepers (Box 91, Folder 60)
    - Archival Episode 6: Ralph Reed, Logged Archive (Box 91, Folder 61)
    - Archival Episode 6: Regent University (Box 91, Folder 62)
    - Archival Episode 6: Robertson Defeat (Box 91, Folder 63)
    - Archival Episode 6: Schaeffer (Box 91, Folder 64)
    - Archival Episode 6: Sex Ed/Abstinence (Box 91, Folder 65)
    - Archival Episode 6: Stealth (Box 91, Folder 66)
    - Archival Episode 6: Summit Ministries (Box 91, Folder 67)
    - Archival Episode 6: 700 Club Wishlist (Box 91, Folder 68)
    - Archival Episode 6: Tax Rhetoric (Box 91, Folder 69)
    - Archival Episode 6: Randell Terry (Box 91, Folder 70)
    - Archival Episode 6: Christian Coalition and Clarence Thomas (Box 91, Folder 71)
    - Archival Episode 6: Time Markers (Box 91, Folder 72)
    - Archival Episode 6: Webster (Box 91, Folder 73)
    - Archival Episode 6: War Rhetoric (Box 91, Folder 74)
    - Archival Episode 6: Weyrich (Box 91, Folder 75)
    - Archival Episode 6: Wider Net (Box 91, Folder 76)
    - Archival Episode 6: Wichita (Box 91, Folder 77)
    - Archival Episode 6: Woodbridge (Box 91, Folder 78)
- Series III: Broadcasters and Broadcasting, 1975-1978 and undated (Boxes 92 -98)
  - Outline (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Current Outline (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Media Evangelism Research (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Introduction (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Actua Service (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - History of Evangelism: A Great Cloud of Witnesses (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Give the Winds A Mighty Voice (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - History (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Soul-Winners (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Soulwinner - Overview (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Special Ministries (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - What Mean These Signs? Prophecy (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Prophecy Manuscript (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Part II - The Constituted Means - Introduction (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Radio - TV Industry (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Audience (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Signs, Gifts, and Wonders (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Positive Thinking: Randell Terry Ministry (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Blessers (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Abundant Life (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Miscellaneous Positive Thinkers (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - Seed Faith (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Positive Thinkers Notes (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - Minor Leagues (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Healers (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - Healing - History (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - Healing - Manuscript to be Edited (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - Healing - Key Papers (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - Praise the Lord Club (Box 92, Folder 29)
  - Healing - Internal Explanations (Evangelists) (Box 92, Folder 30)
  - Healing - External Explanations (Psychology, Sociology) (Box 92, Folder 31)
  - Healing - Miscellaneous (Box 92, Folder 32)
  - Outlines - Processed, Rough Draft (Box 92, Folder 33)
  - Processed - Trash (Box 92, Folder 34)
  - Tongues (Box 92, Folder 35)
  - Basic Sources - Harrell, James, Morris, Simson (Box 92, Folder 36)
  - Point of Contact (Box 92, Folder 37)
  - Glossalalia (Box 92, Folder 38)
  - Saints or Chariatans? (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Radio and Television (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Issues Processed (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Audiences - Issues (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Audience Rado/TV Christian (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Media Myths (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Television - Christian (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Audience (1 of 2) (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Audience (2 of 2) (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Religious Television: Individual Program Summaries (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Radio Ratings (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Finances (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Financial Documents (1 of 3) (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Financial Documents (2 of 3) (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Financial Documents (3 of 3) (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Word of Knowledge (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Dramatic Signs (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Overview (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Blessers (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Prophets (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Prophecy Notes (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Prophecy (1 of 2) (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Prophecy (2 of 2) (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Prophecy Chapter Notes (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Processed Prophecy (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Conservatives (Religo-Patriotism) (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Patriots (1 of 2) (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Patriots (2 of 2) (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Hargis, Billy James (1 of 3) (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Hargis, Billy James (2 of 3) (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Hargis, Billy James (3 of 3) (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Contents of McIntire Publications, 1974-1976 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - McIntire, Carl (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - Harris/McIntire Newspaper (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Hargis (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - Religious Broadcasting and Tele - Evangelists (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Pickle Hearings, 1987-10-07 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Scandals (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Christian Radio-TV Industry Processes (1 of 2) (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Christian Radio-TV Industry Processes (2 of 2) (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Religious Radio/TV Industry, Stations etc. (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - TV - Processed (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Processed - Language, Holding, and Presentation (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - IRS (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - Promotion (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Media Pitch (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - EP - Illustrations (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Issues and Effects - Christianity (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Mail - Duplicate, Xerox (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Finances (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Problems - Financial (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - Budget - Expenses (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - General - Wills, Trusts, etc. Savings (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - "Teams"/Clubs (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Special Occasions (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - Telethons (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Empires (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - Personal Finances (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Christian Finances (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Wall Street Journal Article (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Audience - Who Listens (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - Appeal (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Holding an Audience (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - Sociology (1 of 2) (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - Sociology (2 of 2) (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - Method (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - Speeches (Box 95, Folder 32)
  - Miscellaneous Non - Mail Techniques (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Mail - Handwritten Notes (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Mail (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Wall Street Journal - Documentation - To be Returned (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Christian Mailings (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Mail - Processed (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Mail - Prophets (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Mail - Miscellaneous (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Causes - Misc. (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Mail Article (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Cruise Trips (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Emergency (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Family (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Friends of Evangelists Writing (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Intimacy Confidentiality (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Orphans (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Enemies (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Envelopes (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Ethical Problems (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - "God Told Me" (Visions, etc.) (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Patriotism (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Prayer Requests (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Premiums - General (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Gift Offers (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Jewelry - Pins etc. (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Prayer Cloths (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Sacrifice (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - Special Days - Holidays, Anniversary etc. (Box 96, Folder 28)
  - Specific Amounts (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - Sympathy (Box 96, Folder 30)
  - Units (Box 96, Folder 31)
  - Processing Mail (Box 96, Folder 32)
  - Mail - Data (1 of 2) (Box 96, Folder 33)
  - Mail - Data (2 of 2) (Box 96, Folder 34)
  - Money - Tactics - Misc. (Box 96, Folder 35)
  - Books, Cassettes, Records (Including Bibles) (Box 96, Folder 36)
  - Revival Pitch (Box 96, Folder 37)
  - Hucksters (Box 96, Folder 38)
  - Perry Desmond, 1975-05-12-1975-05-13 (Box 97, Cassette 1)
  - John Douglas - WME - Dallas, Small Radio Ministry (Box 97, Cassette 2)
  - Charles Colon on 700 Club. (Box 97, Cassette 3)
  - Pat Robertson Campaign Tape (Box 97, Cassette 4)
  - Ron Thomasson - Dallas, 1975-01-23 (Box 97, Cassette 5)
  - P. Robertson (Box 97, Cassette 6)
  - Ed Steel D.C., 1976 (Box 97, Cassette 7)
  - Armstrong Hopkins (Box 97, Cassette 8)
  - David E. Harrell Interview of Mary Smith, 1972-07-24 (Box 97, Cassette 9)
  - 700 Club/Pat Robertson, 1975-10-08 (Box 97, Cassette 10)
  - Christian Center Concepts (Box 97, Cassette 11)
  - Christian Jew Foundation, San Antonio, 1978-06-20 (Box 97, Cassette 12)
  - David Terrell - Abstract (Box 97, Cassette 13)
  - Theocracy in America? The Religious Right's Political Agenda (Box 97, Cassette 14)
  - Robertson (Box 97, Cassette 15)
  - CBN - Scott Hessek, Phyllis McNall, 1975-10-08 (Box 97, Cassette 16)
  - CBN - Scott Hessek, Jim Bramlett, 1975-10-08 (Box 97, Cassette 17)
  - CBN - Baerwolf (Box 97, Cassette 18)
  - CBN - J. Smith (Box 97, Cassette 19)
  - Fred Dienert/Ed Steele, 1976-02-25 (Box 97, Cassette 20)
  - Swaggart: Suffer the Children (Box 97, Cassette 21)
  - Swaggart, 1992-11-30 (Box 97, Cassette 22)
  - Jack Van Impe: Is God a Christian, 1981-08-09 (Box 97, Cassette 23)
  - Rev. Al - San Antonio, 1977-06-27 (Box 97, Cassette 24)
  - National Council of Churches Consultation on Electronic Church, 1980 (Box 97, Cassette 25)
  - Religious Right Files (Box 98)
  - Chapters 1-8 drafts (Box 98)
- Series IV: Evangelists, 1975-1990 and undated (Boxes 99-121)
  - Subseries A: Billy Graham (Boxes 99-109)
    - Addresses (Box 99, Folder 1)
      Folder includes handwritten notes and notes about addresses and people associated with Billy Graham.
    - Billy Graham Center Archives (1 of 3) (Box 99, Folder 2)
      Folder includes an annotated thesis or article "A Theology for Racism: Southern Fundamentalists and the Civil Rights Movement" by Bill Leonard. There was also a 1986 article from Christian Scholar's Review "The Evangelical Kaleidoscope and the Call to Christian Unity."
    - Billy Graham Center Archives (2 of 3) (Box 99, Folder 3)
      Folder includes a magazine for "Planning for the Archival Profession," an annotated article from American Archivist "Who Controls the Past," and article from the Winter 1977 "The Historian and Archival Finding Aids." Finally, an archive list with Evangelical/Fundamentalist material, and handwritten notes about Archives.
    - Billy Graham Center Archives (3 of 3) (Box 99, Folder 4)
      Folder incldues microfilm lists, correspondence from Billy Graham Center, pamphlet, newsletter, and a list of collections from Billy Graham Center.
    - General: Ideas, Outlines, etc. (Box 99, Folder 5)
      Folder includes handwritten notes on Martin's research projects and proposal along with a long email by Martin about his research.
    - Bibliography (Box 99, Folder 6)
      Folder includes Billy Graham notes and articles from 1949-1986, an annotated article about evangelical books, and Billy Graham related books. There was also an Index to Religious Periodical Literature from Evangelical Faith and Billy Graham, a table of contents from different books, and a highlighted collection about Billy Graham.
    - Correspondence (1 of 2) (Box 99, Folder 7)
      Folder includes correspondence from the late 1980s to the early 1990s, between Martin and members of the evangelical community about his Billy Graham historical piece, and emails with the secretary to Billy Graham about the production of a documentary about Graham. The folder includes correspondence with Graham himself from 1986-1991, cards from Billy Graham, and correspondence between colleagues about the Graham account, handwritten and email correspondence about the Graham book. Finally there was a copy of Martin's article from Texas Monthly,
    - Correspondence (2 of 2) (Box 99, Folder 8)
      Folder includes email correspondence about video cassettes, notes and responses to editorial suggestions about the Graham work with Maria Guarnaschelli, his editor at William Morrow, and handwritten notes to Guarnaschelli. There was also reviews of "A Prophet with Honor," highly annotated footnote list, correspondence about Martin's book with the Billy Graham Center Archive, and a postcard from Billy Graham, newsletters, pamphlets, and letters from the Billy Graham Center Archive.
    - Response to Book (Box 99, Folder 9)
      Article includes correspondence with a review of the manuscript "A Prophet with Honor," and handwritten reviews of a Billy Graham book, a copy of The John Howard Sanden Newsletter, and editorial comments.
    - Contacts (Box 99, Folder 10)
      Folder includes handwritten notes and call logs with people Martin should contact again, business cards, and people in the evangelical community. There was also information about people in publishing, and TV work, annotated contact list.
    - Crusades (1 of 2) (Box 99, Folder 11)
      Folder includes Billy Graham Crusade Statistics from 1947-1989 on attendance and inquirers, an alphabetical list of locations and chronological list of places, from the Billy Graham Evangelical Archives and Crusade Information Service and a pamphlet from the Billy Graham School of Evangelism.
    - Crusades (2 of 2) (Box 99, Folder 12)
      Folder includes an annotated pamphlet about the Crusade, news releases, and an annotated Graham Crusade newsletter, a thesis from Helenski "Two Crusades: Billy Graham at Yale, 1957, 1982" annotated news clippings from Graham's crusades, and a chapter from "The Billy Graham Crusade." There was also infomation about the general media reception of Crusades across the United States and the wider world.
    - Crusades: Impact (Box 99, Folder 13)
      Folder includes a letter from the Billy Graham School of Evangelism, and an interview with Roger Mahony, the archbishop of Los Angeles,in USA Today. There was also an edited summary about the Crusade, newspaper articles about Graham's crusades in New York City and Hong Kong, notes from the Arkansas Crusade, and crusades in the United Kingdom.
    - Crusades: Results (Box 99, Folder 14)
      Folder includes annotated information from Graham's crusades, an article in Christianity Today, and a pamphlet from the Pacific Northwest Billy Graham Center. There was also a chapter or section from The Pastor's "Church Growth Handbook," and a chapter from The Psychology of Christian Conversion by Ferm. Finally there was an article "Counting Souls: A Study of Counseling at Evangelical Crusades," and another about the statistical effectiveness of these crusades.
    - Crusades: Issues (Box 99, Folder 15)
      Folder includes a letter about electronic evangelism, an interview about the effectiveness of different styles of Evangelism, and an annotated article from The Unchurched "Does the Electronic Church Hurt the Local Church?" There was also handwritten notes about the effectiveness of televangelism and news transcripts about televangelism.
    - 1970s (Box 99, Folder 16)
      Folder includes opinion article from The Guardian, and an article from the Edmonton Crusade.
    - London, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 17)
      Folder included scanned newspaper accounts of Billy Graham's crusade in London set in 1954 and handwritten notes. Also includes annotated news articles of the account and including some by associates of Billy Graham.
    - Greater Washington Billy Graham Crusade, 1996-05 (Box 99, Folder 18)
      Folder includes pamphlets and information about the crusades.
    - Love - In - Action (Box 99, Folder 19)
      Folder includes information from the Love in Action campaign.
    - Operation Andrew (Box 99, Folder 20)
      Folder includes information on Operation Andrew, program to bring new people to church.
    - Publicity (Box 99, Folder 21)
      Folder includes publicity for the Operation Andrew campaign
    - Special Events (Box 99, Folder 22)
    - Ushers (Box 99, Folder 23)
      Folder includes information about the Ushers for the crusades campaign
    - Women (Box 99, Folder 24)
      Folder includs information about the role of women in the Washington edition of the Billy Graham Crusade
    - Youth (Box 99, Folder 25)
      Folder includes information about the role of youths in the crusade.
    - Minister (Box 99, Folder 26)
    - News Update (Box 99, Folder 27)
    - Misc. Documents (Box 99, Folder 28)
    - Follow-Up (Box 99, Folder 29)
    - Congregation Leaders (Box 99, Folder 30)
    - Counseling (Box 99, Folder 31)
    - Co-Labor (Box 99, Folder 32)
    - Christian Life Witness (Box 99, Folder 33)
    - Choir (Box 99, Folder 34)
    - Military (Box 99, Folder 35)
    - A-V Information (Box 99, Folder 36)
    - Finance (Box 99, Folder 37)
    - Crusade Rallies (Box 99, Folder 38)
    - Fundamentalism (1 of 2) (Box 99, Folder 39)
      Folder includes information on Metro Toronto's Billy Graham Crusade, and an article by Billy Graham in the Saturday Evening Post. There was also a copy of an interview of Dr. Billy Graham with a Moscow news member. In addition there was a 1987 issue from Christian Crusade Newspaper, and editions of the Christian Beacon from the 1976-1980s and the Tulsa Tribune.
    - Fundamentalism (2 of 2) (Box 99, Folder 40)
      Folder includes information about Billy Graham and Catholicism, along with supplements from "What's Wrong With Key '73?" and an article from Massey about Falwell and Graham.
    - Films (Box 99, Folder 41)
      Folder includes notes about the film "Africa on the Bridge" and other films, and biographies of Christian Film Ministries Chuck Tatum and pamphlets about christian films.
    - Family (Box 99, Folder 42)
      Folder includes notes and a newspaper article about Billy Graham's family and their relationship with Evangelism.
    - Evangelicalism (Box 99, Folder 43)
      Folder includes handwritten notes on evangelicism and a magazine article "The Year of The Evangelical '76" with some annotations.
    - Ecumenism (Box 99, Folder 44)
      Folder includes information about Catholic conversion and news articles from Christianity Today. There is also handwritten notes, and notes from December 7, 1998 on Ecumeism pg. 1-10.
    - Editorial Notes (Box 99, Folder 45)
      Article includes editorial comments about Martin's "A Prophet with Honor" along with annotations of on the editorial comments,the main comment about the manuscript is that it was repetitive, and William Morrow Style Matters fax from 1991.
    - France, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 46)
      Folder includes information about the Mission France crusade with Billy Graham in September 1986.
    - Christian Beacon, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 47)
      Folder includes an edition of the Christian Beacon from the 1980s
    - Edgar Bundy Ministry (Box 99, Folder 48)
      Folder includes a catalogue of Edgar Bundy Ministries and other materials from that ministry.
    - Christian Beacon, 1980-1983 (Box 99, Folder 49)
      Folder includes editions of Christian Beacons
    - Bible for Today, 1988 (Box 99, Folder 50)
      Folder includes Bible for Today News report.
    - Billy Graham Crusade and News Media Information (Box 99, Folder 51)
      Folder includes information from the Billy Graham Crusade and News Media Information, with photos of Graham.
    - Decision Magazine, 1988-1989, 1995, 2001-2002 (Box 99, Folder 52)
      Folder includes articles and editions of and from Decision 1988, 1989, 1995, 2001, 2002, all with articles about or by Billy Graham and evangelism.
    - Conferences: Berlin (Box 100)
    - Conferences:USSR and Eastern Europe (Box 100)
    - Conferences: Lausanne (Box 100)
    - Conferences: Amsterdam 83/96 (Box 100)
    - England 84/85 (Box 100)